

# CONTACT

+55 (41) 99794-3868 DIEGOALMDA@GMAIL.COM

CURITIBA, PR, BRAZIL

#### **PORTFOLIO:**

HTTPS://WWW.DIEGOALMEIDA.TECH

## **PROFILE**

I am a Telematics technologist graduated in 2013 and a freelance full-stack developer since 2020. I have been dedicated to studying the JavaScript language and some frameworks related to it, My professional interests at the moment include ReactJS, NodeJS and React Native, but I am always open to discover new technologies and continue to learn some new stuff according to the evolutionary trends of the Technology by itself.

# SKILLS

- JavaScript / TypeScript
- React<u>JS</u>
- React Native
- Jest
- Node.js
- Express.js
- Next.is
- API REST / GraphQL
- SQL and NoSQL databases
- HTML5
- CSS3
- Git
- Figma

# DIEGO DE ALMEIDA CUNHA

# SOFTWARE ENGINEER

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### FREELANCER AS WEB DEVELOPER

SELF EMPLOYED | MAR 2020 - PRESENT

- Created funtional websites and the interface layout for usability.
- Main Technologies: ReactJS, Node.js, Javascript, HTML, CSS.

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

ITS IMPORTAÇÃO, TECNOLOGIA E SERVIÇOS | AUG 2021 - FEB 2022

- Systems and apps development and maintenance. Modify programs, changing encoding and other elements. Fix bugs and make system changes to support new needs.
- Main Technologies: ReactJS, React Native, Javascript, HTML, CSS.

## COMMERCIAL ATTENDANT

EMPRESA BRASILEIRA DE CORREIOS E TELÉGRAFOS | MAR 2013 -FEB 2021

- Performes customer service and sell mail office products
- Managed a Brazilian Federal Post Office and signed contracts with some local companies

## TECHNICAL SUPPORT AND WEB DEVELOPER

TECHNICAL SOLUÇÕES EM INFORMÁTICA LTDA | FEB 2012 - MAR 2013

- Installed and configured the telecommunication equipments
- Create and maintain websites

## **EDUCATION**

## TECHNOLOGIST IN TELEMATICS

INSTITUTO FEDERAL DE EDUCAÇÃO, CIÊNCIA E TECNOLOGIA DA PARAÍBA 2008 - 2013

• Programming languages, computer network, telecommunication

## ONLINE COURSES

- Complete course of Javascript from beginner to master 2020.
- Complete course of NodeJS and MongoDB developer 2020.
- Full Stack Developer 2020
- Rocketseat ReactJS, NodeJS, React Native Practical content, projects and performance challenges 2022.
- Main Technologies: HTML5 CSS3 JavaScript Node.js ReactJS Vue React Native TypeScript Next.js NestJs RestAPI CI/CD AWS.

#### **WEB DESIGN**

FÁCIL CENTRO DE CAPACITAÇÃO PROFISSIONAL | 2010

• Photoshop, Corel Draw, FTP, Dreamweaver, HTML, CSS, Flash and projects

## REFERENCES

https://github.com/diegoalmda

https://www.linkedin.com/in/diegoalmda/